Guide to the Stanford University Postcard Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Postcards (individual)
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 754; Color Print
    Caption: East Gate, Stanford University, Stanford, California. East gate of the quadrangle of sandstone classrooms at Stanford looks out on the university library. Towering over the red tiled roof of the Quad is the 285-foot Hoover library.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 755; Color Print
    Imprint: R.and C. Hakanson
  - Inner Quad, 1/21/1976; 756; Color Print
    Caption: Towers, Stanford University, Stanford, Calif. Two towers flank Stanford's quadrangle of 12 sandstone classroom buildings. Around the inner quadrangle is built a second set of 14 buildings, all in the old California MIssion style and connected by covered archways.
    Addressed to: Mr. Barotolme Cortes, 83-15 118 St. appt 2H, Ken Gardens, New York 11415
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 757; Photo
    Gift of Director of Information-3/1/53
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 758; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 759; B/W Print
    Caption: Arcade. Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 760; B/W Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 761; Photo
    Caption: Portico Stanford University Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 762; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 763; B/W Print
    Gift of Wm. Moran, La Canada, Calif.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 764; Photo
    Caption: A Stanford Arcade. Stanford University
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 765; B/W Print
  - Inner Quad, n.d; 766; B/W Print
    Caption: No. 4. Arcades, Stanford University, Cal.
    Gift of MIss Elizabeth Thompson, 11/18/58
  - Inner Quad, 12/25/1910; 767; Photo
    Caption: Leland Stanford Jr. University, Palo Alto, Cal. 86
    Message: Merry Christmas and a prosperous, happy New Year. Jo
    Addressed to: Mrs. C. W. Thomas, Woodland, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 768; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 769; Photo
  - Inner Quad, 7/11/1910; 770; Sepia Print
    Message: Dear [illegible] Thought you would like this for your collection. How is litte Fritzie as well as yourselves. All are well again at home. Reached home last Monday about 10:00 feeling fine but of course mother was a little tired. Love from all. Gus
    Addressed to: Mr. F.E. Brasch, 920 Scott St., Palo Alto, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 771; Sepia Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 772; Color Print
    Caption: No. 29. Chemistry Building, through the Arches, Stanford University, California
    Imprint: Hyde's Book Store (The Albertype Co.)
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 773; Sepia Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 774; Sepia Print
    Caption: Arcades and Chemistry Building, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 775; Photo
    Caption: A Stanford Arcade Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 776; B/W Print
    Caption: Arcade, Stanford University, Cal. 251.
    Imprint: Bardell Art Co.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 777; Color Print
    Caption: No. 35. Arcade at Entrance to Memorial Church, Stanford University, California
    Imprint: E.L Hyde
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 778; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 779; Tinted Print
    Caption: On the Stanford Quadrangle, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 780; B/W Print
    Caption: Corridor and Entrance to Memorial Church, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 781; Tinted Print
    Caption: 415 - Arcade, Stanford University, California
    Imprint: E.P. Charlton and Co.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 782; Sepia Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 783; B/W Print
    Caption: No. 1. Arcade A, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 784; B/W Print
    Caption: No. 3. Arcades C, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 785; Sepia Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 786; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 787; Sepia Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 788; Sepia Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 789; Color Print
    Caption: 2172 - View Through the Arches, Stanford University, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 790; Sepia Print
    Caption: 1505 - Throught the Arches, Leland Stanford Jr. University, Palo Alto, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 791; B/W Print
    Caption: Quad View, Stanford
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 792; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 793; Sepia Print
    Caption: The Inner Quadrangle Stanford University
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 794; Photo
    Original library later law library
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 795; Sepia Print
  - Inner Quad, 12/31/1909; 796; Photo
    Caption: Side Entrance Inner Quadrangle, Stanford University Palo Alto. California
    Message: Happy New Year wishes from Mother. Hannah B. Bell
    Addressed to: Anna J. Poofier, San Jose, Calif-
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 797; Tinted Print
    Caption: At Stanford University, Palo Alto, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 798; Photo
    Caption: East Gateway, Stanford.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 799; Sepia Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 800; Sepia Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 801; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 802; B/W Print
    Caption: Through the Inner Quadrangle, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 803; Photo
    The Inner Quadrangle of Stanford University from the Church (in reconstruction)
  - Inner Quad, 1978; 804; Color Print
    Caption: Inner Quadrangle, Stanford University
    Imprint: John Wagner
  - Inner Quad, 1978; 805; Color Print
    Caption: The Quadrangle from Hoover Tower, Stanford University
  - Inner Quad, undated; 2016-007.2 (Box 2)
  - Quad - Miscellaneous Views, 1907; 806; Photo
    Message: Dear Mrs. Garber:- Your letter received. Glad to hear from you. We enjoy thinking of our visit with you so much. Mr. Schofield wants to get some more pictures taken off and then he will send the films. glad you are enjoying "our" Indian basket. Sincerely Mantro N.S.
    Addressed to: Mrs. J.B. Garber, Dunkirk, Jay Co., Indiana
    Gift of Mary Schofield
    Quad - Miscellaneous Views
  - Quad - Miscellaneous Views, Undated; 807; B/W Print
    Caption: No. 7. Stanford University, Cal.
  - Quad - Miscellaneous Views, Undated; 808; Photo
  - Quad - Miscellaneous Views, 809; B/W Print
    View of Quadrangle from the North.
  - Quad - Miscellaneous Views, Undated; 810; B/W Print
    Caption: The Quadrangle, Stanford University, Cal.
    Imprint: E.C. Kropp Co.
  - Quad - Miscellaneous Views, Undated; 811; Tinted Print
  - Quad - Miscellaneous Views, Undated; 812; Photo
  - Quad - Miscellaneous Views, Undated; 813; B/W Print
    Caption: A Stanford Drive, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Quad - Miscellaneous Views, Undated; 814; B/W Print
    Caption: West View, Stanford
  - Quad - Miscellaneous Views, Undated; 815; Tinted Print
    Estate of Zoe Watkins Johnson May '82
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 816; Tinted Print
    Caption: Lagunita and General View of Stanford University, California
    Quad View over Lake Lagunita
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 817; Color Print
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 818; Color Print
    Caption: Birdseye View, Leland Stanford Jr. University, Palo Alto, Cal.
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, 7/1/1920; 819; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford University, San Jose, Cal.
    Message: Dear Mother, I heard that Grandpa Hall died. Write about it to Robert Pescerdo. Your son, Roy.
    Imprint: E. von Bardeleben
    Addressed to: Mrs. J. Bailer, 434 So. 7th St., San Jose, Calif.
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 820; Color Print
    Caption: General View, Stanford University and Lake
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 821; Photo
    Bird's Eye View of Stanford University form the hills. San Francisco Bay may be faintly seen in the distance (3 or 4 miles away) in front of the hazy hills.
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 822; Sepia Print
    Caption: Stanford University from the Hills
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 823; Sepia Print
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 824; Sepia Print
    Caption: The Lagunita Stanford University
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 825; Sepia Print
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 826; Sepia Print
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 827; Sepia Print
    Caption: Stanford University The Lagunita
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 828; Sepia Print
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, 7/29/1908; 829; Color Print
    Caption: Lake Lagunita and General View, Stanford University, Cal.
    Message: Hello Kid, got your postal O.K. Thanks for reminding Rose about that postal. Well Kid are you people making lots of money in the fruit, well you better save up, you know this is leap year ha-ha remind Rose of it. I hardly think it will do any good. Ha Ha Jack
    Addressed to: Miss Mable Enos, Hollister, Calif.
  - Quad View over Lake Lagunita, Undated; 830; B/W Print
    View of Quad from the "Look Out" on Lathrop Estate pre - earthquake
  - Roble Gym, Undated; 831; Color Print
    Caption: No. 47 Women's Gynasium Stanford University California
    Roble Gym
  - Roble Hall I, Undated; 832; Color Print
    Caption: 739- Roble Hall, Stanford University, California
    Roble Hall
  - Roble Hall I, Undated; 833; B/W Print
    Caption: Roble hall, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Roble Hall I, Undated; 834; Color Print
    Caption: Roble hall, Stanford University, California
    Imprint: E.P. Charlton & Co.
  - Roble Hall I, Undated; 835; B/W Print
    Caption: Roble Hall - Stanford
  - Roble Hall I, Undated; 836; Sepia Print
    Caption: Roble Hall, Stanford Univesity, Cal.
    no chimneys, possible post-06 Quake?
  - Roble Hall II, Undated; 837; B/W Print
  - Roble Hall II, Undated; 838; Photo
    Caption: Roble Hall Stanford University Palo Alto
    Photograph is B & W
  - Roble Hall II, n.d; 839; Tinted Print
    Caption: Roble Hall, Stanford Univesity Cal. 4904
  - Roble Hall I, 14 Dec, 1906; 840; Color Print
    Caption: Roble Hall, Stanford University, California
    Message: Miss Annie Fenton
    Salinas Cal
    Star Route
  - Roble Hall I, Undated; 841; B/W Print
    Caption: Roble Hall, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Roble Walk Through Corridor of Trees, 9 Jan, 1912; 842; Sepia Print
    Caption: Roble Walk, Stanford University
  - Roble Walk Through Corridor of Trees, Undated; 843; Sepia Print
  - San Francisquito Creek, Undated; 844; Sepia Print
    Caption: 508 San Francisquito, Stanford University, California
    San Francisquito Creek
  - San Francisquito Creek, Undated; 845; Color Print
    Caption: San Francisquito Creek, near Stanford University
  - San Francisquito Creek, Undated; 846; Color Print
    Caption: San Francisquito, Stanford University, California
  - San Francisquito Creek, Undated; 847; B/W Print
    Caption: San Francisquito Creek, Stanoford University, Cal.
  - San Francisquito Creek, Undated; 848; B/W Print
    Caption: San Francisquito Creek, Stanford University, Cal.
  - San Francisquito Creek, none; 849; B/W Print
    Caption: No. 14 Foot Bridge, Stanford University, Cal
    Imprint: Hydes's Book s Store,
  - Foot Bridge, n.d; 850; Sepia Print
    Caption: No. 14. Foot Bridge, Stanford University, Cal.
    Message: I was greatly pleased this afternoon when Professor Drew said that my equipment was very good. I didn't pat myself on the back because I knew it wasn't due. I was the one one of three girls who had it so I felt fine - Thanks to you.
    Ruby
    duplicate of no. 849
  - San Francisquito Creek, Undated; 851; Sepia Print
    Message: Hope you and mother are having a nice time, and also will stay there [ ] [ ]. I am getting along nicely [ ] I [ ] [ ] [ ] [ ]
    Daddy
  - Bridge over Creek, n.d; 852; Sepia Print
    Caption: The Foot Bridge, Stanford University, Cal.
  - San Francisquito Creek, Undated; 853; Color Print
    Caption: 741-San Francisquito, Stanford Univesity, California
  - San Francisquito Creek, Undated; 854; B/W Print
  - Searsville Lake, n.d; 855; Color Print
    Caption: Searsville Lake and Park. Woodside, Calif.
    White sandy beach, picnicking in shady groves, miles of trails for hiking and equestrian paths. Very popular with millions of people in the Bay Area and on the Penensula.
    Searsville Lake (Calif.)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta House, Undated; 856; Sepia Print
    Caption: Kappa Alpha Theta Sorority, Stanford University, Cal.
    Sorority - Kappa Alpha Theta
  - Alpha Phi House, Undated; 857; Sepia Print
    Caption: Alpha Phi Sorority, Stanford University, Cal.
    Sorority - Alpha Phi
  - Alpha Phi House, Undated; 858; B/W Print
    Caption: Alpha Phi
  - Kappa House, Undated; 859; B/W Print
    Caption: Kappa Kappa Gamma Sorority, Stanford University, Cal.
    Sorority - Kappa Kappa Gamma
  - Delta Delta Delta House, Undated; 860; Sepia Print
    Caption: Delta Delta Delta Sorority, Stanford University, Cal.
    Sorority - Delta Delta Delta
  - Football Staduim, Undated; 861; Tinted Print
    Caption: (Back) Situated on Stanford Univesity Campus, amid attractive and quiet surroundings, Stanford Stadum, the nation's second largest, will accomodate 100,000 people.
    Stadium
  - Football Stadium, Undated; 862; Color Print
    Caption: PA4:-Stadium. Stanford Univesity, Palo Alto, California
  - Football Stadium, Undated; 863; Tinted Print
    Caption: Stadium Stanford University, California
    Imprint: The Albertype Co.; Hyde's Book Store
  - Football Stadium, 1957; 864; Color Print
    Caption: (Front) Stanford Stadium
    Lots of Free parking adjacent to the stadium
    Easy to get in- Easy to get out
    Easily Accessible
    By Trane, Plane
    Bus or Car!!!
    (Rear) 1957 Schedule
    1957 football schedule on back
  - Football Stadium, 7-Jun-76; 865; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford Stadium, Stanford University Palo Alto, California
    Breathtaking aerial view of this over 90,000 seat stadium, site of many action-packed football games and other athletic contests.
    Message: in Spanish
  - Angel of Grief, post 1906; 866; Tinted Print
    Caption: The Angel of Grief - Stanford University, CAL S-574
  - Memorial Church (Interior), post 1906; 868; Sepia Print
    Reverse caption: On the "Road of a Thousand Wonders"
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 869; B/W Print
  - Stanford Barn exterior, 1966; 870; Color Print
    reverse caption: OLD BARN, Stanford University at Palo Alto, California dates back to 1888. etc.
    Stanford Barn (Old Winery)
  - Stanford Family Statue, 871; Sepia Print
    Caption: 1897 - The Stanford Group, Stanford University, California
    Stanford Family Statue
  - Parade, outer quad, Stanford University, 872; Sepia Print
    Imprint: Stanford University Archives
    reverse caption: Students and Faculty parade down Lasuen, adjacent to outer quad, Stanford University, c. 1912
    Stanford Historical Society - Reproductions of Old Photos
  - Inner Courtyard of the Quadrangle, Stanford University, 873; Sepia Print
    reverse caption: The inner courtyard of the Quadrangle, Stanford University, C. 1905
  - Stanford Rooting Section, Big Game, 874; Sepia Print
    reverse caption: The Stanford rooting section, Big Game, 1908
  - Leland Stanford Family, 875; Sepia Print
    Imprint: Stanford university Archives
    reverse caption: The Leland Stanford family: Leland, Jane and Leland, Jr.
  - The "Little German Band", 876; Sepia Print
    reverse caption: The "Little German Band," 1907, a precurser of the Leland Stanford, Jr., University Marching Band?
  - Transportation on Stanford campus, carriage, adjacent to outer quad, 877; Sepia Print
    reverse caption: Transportation on the Stanford campus, c. 1905
  - Stanford Students Camping in Front of Encina Hall Dormitory, 878; Sepia Print
    reverse caption: Stanford students camping in front of Encina Hall dormitory after the earthquake, April 1906
  - Stanford Campus exterior, 879; Sepia Print
    reverse caption: View of the Stanford campus from across Lake Lagunita, c. 1905
  - Quadrangle of Stanford University, 880; Sepia Print
    Imprint: STanford University Archives
    reverse caption: Pre-earthquake view, c. 1905, of the Quadrangle, still the academic center of the Stanford University campus
  - Front of Memorial Church after earthquake, 881; Sepia Print
    reverse caption: Front of Memorial Church following the earthquake, April 1906
  - The new library, present site of the Graduate School of Business, after earthquake, 882; Sepia Print
    reverse caption: The new library ( present site of the Graduate School of Business) was completed just before the earthquake struck, April 1906
  - Entrance gates, Stanford University, before and after earthquake, 883; Sepia Print
    reverse caption: Entrance gates before and after the earthquake, April 1906
  - Fallen Statue of Louis Agassiz during earthquake, front of quadrangle, 884; Sepia Print
    reverse caption: Statue of Louis Agassiz fallen from its perch on the front of the quadrangle during the earthquake, April 1906
  - all male chorus line of "Rambling Rameses", 885; Sepia Print
    reverse caption: The all male chorus line of the student play, "Rambling Rameses," 1912
  - on Stanford Ranch, men working outside, 886; Sepia Print
    Caption: Stanford Ranch Durham Cal.
    Stanford Properties
  - Stanford Durham Ranch, Barns etc., July 14, 887; Sepia Print
  - alfalfa field around trustees house, July 14, 888; Sepia Print
    Caption: Alfalfa Field Durham Cal.
  - Durham Ranch exterior, 889; Sepia Print
  - Durham Ranch exterior, 890; Sepia Print
  - Durham Ranch exterior, 891; Sepia Print
  - two children, New Year's Day on the Durham Ranch, 892; Sepia Print
  - two children, Durham Ranch, 893; Sepia Print
  - Warm Springs Ranch exterior, 894; Tinted Print
    Caption: "Old Mission Peak" and "Warm Springs," Cal.
    Message: Robert B. Crowell...
  - A Cold Winter's Day on Campus, man holding icicle, 895; Sepia Print
    Student life.
  - Stanford Units March on Old Football Field in June 1918, 896; Sepia Print
  - Stanford students on a railway, 897; Sepia Print
  - Female Stanford Students in front quad, 898; Photo
  - female Stanford Students in quad (behind Memorial Church), circa 1910; 899; Photo
  - Stanford students sitting on grass on campus, 900; Sepia Print
  - outside quad., two female Stanford students with parasols, 901; Sepia Print
  - male students outside in inner side of quad, 902; Sepia Print
    Imprint: Randall and Crandall
  - male students in comedic show dressed as females, 903; Sepia Print
    Message: Mr. W. P. Smith...Hello old socks - how's your wife and children? etc.
  - Roughs' Day, Fall 1922Bob Triest (left), Hawley Sumners (right), 904; Sepia Print
  - Roughs' Day, Fall 1922, 905; Sepia Print
    Wm. H. Irwin '25, "Busy" Cain takes my picture!
  - Rally, 906; Photo
    Caption: Rally, nov. 10-10
  - rally in front of Library Building that was gift of Thomas Welston Stanford, 907; Photo
  - line of Stanford male students, 908; Photo
  - male students, sleepover?, 909; Photo
  - athletics, students in the stands, 910; Sepia Print
  - Class of 1916, 911; Sepia Print
  - Frosh-Sophomore Tie-Up, 912; Photo
  - Freshman-Sophomore Ruch, on football field, 913; Photo
    Caption: Freshman-Sophomore Ruch, 1912
  - Frosh-Sophomore Tie-Up, circa 1910-1915, 914; Photo
  - Frosh-Soph Tie-Up, c. 1910-1915, 915; Photo
  - on campus at night, 916; Photo
  - Night Shirt peerade, 1914, 917; Sepia Print
  - Pajamarino, c. 1910-1915, 918; Photo
  - Pajama Parade, 919; Photo
    Message: Dear Uncle Herman, Every year at this time we have what is known as a pajama parade. etc.
  - Nightshirt "Peerade", 920; Photo
    Caption: Nightshirt "Peerade" 1912
  - four hats, 921; B/W Print
  - three hats and a hat with Stanford symbol, 922; Photo
  - male student on Stanford hat looking at advertisement, 923; B/W Print
  - four male students, different headgear, 924; Photo
    Caption: Stanford Class Styles
    Message: shows "Plugs," headgear worn by Juniors; the idea was borrowed from Berkley
  - poster / advertisement, 925; B/W Print
  - advertisement to Freshman, 926; Sepia Print
  - poster, "Sweet Sixteen", 927; Photo
  - poster to Frosh, "The Last and Only Warning of the '23 Class to the Unorganized Rabble of the Frosh", 928; Photo
  - poster, " 1913 presents the Death of the Dirty Dozen", 929; Photo
  - Poster, "Sixteen Statutes for Filthy Frosh", 930; Photo
  - poster, "Freshmen! You Will Smoke In Hell...", 931; Photo
  - poster, "14 PLUGs UGLY 13 or Thirteen In-terred", 932; Photo
  - Toyon exterior, 933; Tinted Print
    Caption: Toyon Hall, Stanford University, California
    Message: Give this card to....
    Toyon Hall
  - Tressidor Memorial Union exterior, 1966; 934; Photo
    reverse caption: TRESIDDER MEMORIAL UNION is the new community center of Stanford University at Palo Alto, California. etc.
    Tressidor Union
  - Stanford Christmas Faire, four shots, 935; Photo
    Message: Abundant crafts, performers and international foods...Bring this postcard to the Faire and participate in a drawing...etc.
    Tresidder Union
  - University Seal, 936; Photo
    University Seal
  - University Seal, 937
    Message: Christmas Greetings from California! Remembering the June days I spent with you at Greene. I wish I could sen you some of the flowers and sunshine of Stanford. Mary C. Dickenson December, 1907
    Imprint: The Chas. H. Elliott Co.
  - White Plaza, 938; Photo
    reverse caption: White Memorial Plaza is at the center of the student activities area of Stanford University. etc.
    White Plaza
  - White Plaza, close-up of fountain, 939; Photo
    reverse caption: An ornamental fountain, created by Aristides Demetrios, a young massachusetts-born scultor, now established in Sand Francisco, is the focal point of the White memorial Plaza at Stanford University in Palo Alto, California. etc.
  - on a road on campus, a worker, 940; Photo
    Workers
  - on road on campus, a worker, 941; Photo
  - Worder outside building, 942; Photo
  - Worder outside building, 943; Photo
  - worker outside of building, 944; Photo
  - worker outside building, 945; Photo
  - worker outside of building, 946; Photo
  - worder outside of building, 947; Photo
  - worker outside of building, 948; Photo
  - worker outside of building, 949; Photo
  - construction worker, 950; Sepia Print
  - worker on road on campus, 951; Photo
  - worker outside of building, 952; Photo
  - worker on the road on campus passed a car, 953; Photo
  - worker outside of building, 954; Photo
  - worker outside of building, 955; Photo
  - Souther Pacific Station exterior, 956; B/W Print
    Imprint: The Albertype Co.
    Palo Alto (Calif.)
  - Southern Pacific Depot exterior with people, 957; B/W Print
    Caption: 1917 - Southern Pacific Depot, palo Alto, California
  - Southern Pacific Depot exterior with people, 958; Sepia Print
    Caption: 1917 - Souther pacific Depot, palo Alto, California
  - Dinah's Shack exterior, 959; Color Print
    Message: How I wish I was there right now. etc.
    reverse caption: During your stay in California visit this unique Restaurant. etc.
  - Rickey's Studio Inn aerial view, 960; Color Print
    Caption: Rickey's Studio Inn, Palo Alto, California
    Imprint: Schwabacher-Prey Co.
  - Rickey's Studio Club exterior, 961; Photo
    Caption: Rickey's Studio Club Palo Alto, California
  - Andre's "L'OMELETTE" interior, 962; Photo
    reverse caption: Andre's "L'OMELETTE" etc.
  - Lytton Ave. School exterior, 963; Color Print
    Caption: Lytton Ave. School, PALO ALTO, Cal.
  - Peninsula Hospital exterior, 964; B/W Print
  - Carnegie Library, 965; Sepia Print
    Caption: CARNEGIE LIBRARY PALO ALTO, CAL.
  - Carnegie Library exterior, 966; Color Print
    Caption: Carnegie Library, PALO ALTO, Cal.
  - Carnegie Library exterior, 967; B/W Print
  - a residence street, 968; Tinted Print
    Caption: A Residence Street, palo Alto, California
    Message: In...
  - California Residence and Grounds, 969; Color Print
    Caption: Palo Alt, Cal.
    "Cal. Residence & Grounds"
    Imprint: Newman post Card Co.